{
    "subject": "resource/The_War_Zone",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Freddie_Cunliffe",
    "human_readable": "The War Zone stars Freddie Cunliffe.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7980196475982666,
            "question": "Has Freddie Cunliffe won any awards for his performance in 'The War Zone'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5994275212287903,
            "question": "Who stars in the movie 'The War Zone'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5760475397109985,
            "question": "Is Freddie Cunliffe an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5458681583404541,
            "question": "Can you tell me the name of a film featuring Freddie Cunliffe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5312685966491699,
            "question": "Are there any other films starring Freddie Cunliffe that you know of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3840581178665161,
            "question": "Who directed 'The War Zone'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3701709508895874,
            "question": "What is the name of the actor who appears in 'The War Zone'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3664998412132263,
            "question": "What is 'The War Zone' about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2653971016407013,
            "question": "What year was 'The War Zone' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2404266744852066,
            "question": "In what genre is the film 'The War Zone' likely to be classified?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The War Zone stars Freddie Cunliffe.",
            "html": "dbpedia_229_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was 'The War Zone' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_229_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is 'The War Zone' about?",
            "html": "dbpedia_229_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the actor who appears in 'The War Zone'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_229_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_229_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_229_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_229_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_229_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_229_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_229_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_229_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_229_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_229_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_229_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Freddie Cunliffe appeared in the film \"The War Zone,\" which supports the statement that he is one of its stars."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}